=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 16=
= الحلقة 16 =
Had a good look?
ألقي نظرة جيدة؟
I was not looking at you.
لم أكن أنظر إليك.
You were in the way of my sunlight.
كنت في طريق ضوء الشمس الخاص بي.
By the way,
على فكرة،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Don't tell me this is a coincidence.
لا تقل لي هذه صدفة.
It is a coincidence.
إنها صدفة.
I just got my routine check-up
لقد حصلت للتو على فحص روتيني
and I saw you get pushed in here.
ورأيتك يتم دفعك هنا.
Cici is handling the admission now
Cici تتعامل مع القبول الآن
and asked me to look after you.
وطلب مني الاعتناء بك.
(Look after me?)
(اعتني بي؟)
(I'm not a child.)
(أنا لست طفلا.)
You're an adult.
أنت بالغ.
Don't you know what you're allergic to?
ألا تعرف ما الذي تشعر بالحساسية تجاهه؟
I remember it was cured a few years ago.
أتذكر أنه تم شفاؤه قبل بضع سنوات.
Besides, I don't usually have sesame seeds.
الى جانب ذلك ، ليس لدي عادة بذور السمسم.
Cici thought you turned suicidal
يعتقد Cici أنك تحولت إلى الانتحار
because of a break-up.
بسبب الانفصال.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Come on.
تعال.
All for that cheater?
كل هذا من أجل الغشاش؟
Tch.
تك.
He's not worth it.
انه لا يستحق كل هذا العناء.
Come.
اتى.
Let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'm not crippled.
أنا لست مشلولاً.
I can do it.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
Just let me enjoy my solitude.
فقط دعني أستمتع بوحدتي.
Fengyan,
فنغيان ،
will you be busy in the next few days?
هل ستكون مشغولا في الايام القليلة القادمة؟
Come buy some baby accessories with me.
تعال اشتري بعض اكسسوارات الاطفال معي.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
I should be free tomorrow.
يجب أن أكون حرة غدا.
May we give birth to a healthy baby.
نرجو أن تلد طفلًا سليمًا.
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Yes.
نعم.
Be mindful when you eat now.
كن حذرًا عندما تأكل الآن.
Sesame seed allergy is no joke.
حساسية بذور السمسم ليست مزحة.
Be vigilant.
كن حذرا.
Noted.
وأشار.
You can leave after you fill out the paperwork.
يمكنك المغادرة بعد ملء الأوراق.
Come.
اتى.
You're her boyfriend. Sign it.
أنت صديقها.  وقعها.
Huh?
هاه؟
Oh.
أوه.
Well,
نحن سوف،
he's my brother.
إنه أخي.
His Chinese is bad
لغته الصينية سيئة
and he can't read.
ولا يستطيع القراءة.
But doctor,
لكن دكتور ،
since I'm already here,
منذ أن أصبحت هنا بالفعل ،
can I get a brain scan?
هل يمكنني الحصول على مسح دماغي؟
Why?
لماذا؟
I haven't been able to sleep well lately
لم أستطع النوم جيدًا مؤخرًا
and I keep having hallucinations.
وما زلت أعاني من الهلوسة.
I think I might have
أعتقد أنني قد يكون لدي
Alzheimer's.
مرض الزهايمر.
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر في ذلك.
You're fine.
أنت بخير.
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
Oh.
أوه.
What?
لما؟
I was checking if you have a fever.
كنت أتحقق مما إذا كان لديك حمى.
Let's wait for Cici outside.
دعنا ننتظر Cici في الخارج.
Make sure you take the meds.
تأكد من تناول الأدوية.
So many meds here.
الكثير من المدس هنا.
How am I supposed to take them?
كيف يفترض بي أن آخذهم؟
Well, Wei.
حسنا وي.
Too bad my Chinese is bad
سيئة للغاية بلدي الصينية سيئة
and I can't read.
ولا أستطيع القراءة.
If they are twins,
إذا كانا توأمان ،
let's call them Jiang Yanyan and Jiang Mengmeng.
دعونا نسميهم جيانغ يانيان وجيانغ مينجمينج.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Or keep up.
أو مواكبة.
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
You saw a friend?
رأيت صديق؟
No.
لا.
I must have mistaken someone.
لابد أنني أخطأت في شخص ما.
My dear, wait for me here.
عزيزي انتظرني هنا.
I'll get a number for us.
سأحصل على رقم لنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Come back soon.
عود قريبا.
(Emergency)
(طارئ)
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
Dr. Xu.
دكتور شو.
Getting a pregnancy check-up with your wife?
إجراء فحص الحمل مع زوجتك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
Your wish has come true.
تحققت امنيتك.
You can finally be a father.
يمكنك أخيرًا أن تكون أبًا.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Right?
حق؟
Oh.
أوه.
Was that
كان ذلك
Xiang Wei just now?
شيانغ وى للتو الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
It was her.
كانت هي.
She was sent here in an emergency.
تم إرسالها هنا في حالة الطوارئ.
Apparently, she got into a shock from a food allergy.
على ما يبدو ، أصيبت بصدمة من حساسية تجاه الطعام.
Food allergy?
حساسية الطعام؟
She is a cautious person.
هي شخص حذر.
She wouldn't ingest something carelessly.
لن تأكل شيئًا بلا مبالاة.
My elevator is here. I'll get going now.
المصعد الخاص بي هنا.  سأذهب الآن.
I'm going down.
أنا ذاهب إلى أسفل.
You followed me?
هل اتبعتني؟
I just want to see you and the baby.
أنا فقط أريد أن أراك والطفل.
Xu Xuan.
شو شوان.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
(File) Mengmeng,
(ملف) مينجمينج ،
you know what I'm talking about.
أنت تعرف ما أتحدث عنه.
The baby is mine, isn't it?
الطفل لي ، أليس كذلك؟
Let's start over, okay?
لنبدأ من جديد ، حسنًا؟
I can take good care of you.
يمكنني الاعتناء بك جيدا.
What are you on about?
ماذا أنت قادم على فعله؟
It's Fengyan's child.
إنه طفل فينجيان.
And the child can only have one father.
ويمكن للطفل أن يكون له أب واحد فقط.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Stop acting tough.
توقف عن التصرف بحزم.
I regret it so much now.
أنا آسف لذلك كثيرا الآن.
I regret that I wasn't more proactive.
يؤسفني أنني لم أكن أكثر نشاطًا.
Stop deluding yourself.
توقف عن خداع نفسك.
And I thought
و أعتقدت
you are the only one who gets me.
أنت الوحيد الذي يحصل علي.
But now, you're forcing me too.
لكن الآن ، أنت تجبرني أيضًا.
And if I insist on staying?
وإذا أصررت على البقاء؟
Mengmeng?
مينجمينج؟
Mengmeng, why are you here?
مينجمينج ، لماذا أنت هنا؟
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
You look so pale.
تبدين شاحبة جدا.
It's nothing.
إنه لاشيء.
I saw a maternity group just now.
رأيت مجموعة أمومة الآن.
They said
قالوا
there would be a future parents seminar tomorrow
سيكون هناك ندوة الآباء في المستقبل غدا
and wanted me to attend it.
وأرادني أن أحضره.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
(How have you been?)
(كيف كان حالك؟)
(I think I saw you in the hospital today. I heard you had an allergy?)
(أعتقد أنني رأيتك في المستشفى اليوم. سمعت أنك مصاب بالحساسية؟)
(Dr. Xu told me to get in touch with you.)
(أخبرني الدكتور شو أن أتواصل معك.)
(My dear.)
(عزيزي.)
(I still have work to do.)
(لا يزال لدي عمل لأقوم به.)
(I'll be back later.)
(سوف اعود لاحقا.)
(Just go to bed.)
(فقط اذهب إلى الفراش.)
(No need to wait for me.)
(لا حاجة لانتظارني.)
(A cheating man)
(رجل غش)
(doesn't care)
(لا يهتم)
(about his wife,)
(عن زوجته)
(let alone his mistress.)
(ناهيك عن عشيقته.)
(I don't know if he loves me.)
(لا أعرف ما إذا كان يحبني).
(What I know)
(ما اعرفه)
(is that he doesn't love you as much as you imagine.)
(هو أنه لا يحبك بقدر ما تتخيل).
(Sorry.)
(آسف.)
(It's my fault.)
(هذا خطأي.)
(Will you forgive me?)
(سوف يغفر لي؟)
(Private Residence)
(سكن خاص)
♪Time might stop♪
♪ الوقت قد يتوقف ♪
♪The bitterness from having your soul torn apart♪
مرارة تمزق روحك
♪Hard to get out♪
♪ صعب الخروج ♪
♪Of this shackle♪
من هذا القيد ♪
♪I am drowning in this cycle♪
أنا أغرق في هذه الحلقة ♪
♪How many times have I been exploited?♪
♪ كم مرة تم استغلالي؟
♪Who is responsible for the indifference♪
من المسؤول عن اللامبالاة
♪Under the neon signs?♪
♪ تحت إشارات النيون؟
♪Swallowing this bitterness time after time♪
ابتلاع هذه المرارة مرة بعد مرة
♪Who is hiding among the clouds?♪
من يختبئ بين السحاب؟
♪I float like a feather♪
♪ أسبح كالريشة ♪
♪As I land♪
♪ كما هبطت ♪
♪Amplify this rebirth, I am awakening♪
تضخيم هذه الولادة الجديدة ، أنا أستيقظ ♪
♪Life is disappearing, It's getting tougher♪
♪ الحياة تختفي ، تزداد صعوبة ♪
♪We merely passed by each other before we fell♪
"لقد مررنا ببعضنا البعض قبل أن نسقط"
♪One more time♪
♪ مرة أخرى ♪
♪Abandon the bond and the vanity♪
ترك الرابطة والغرور ♪
♪Shatter the gossip and the criticisms♪
تحطيم الثرثرة والانتقادات
♪The final silhouette♪
♪ الصورة الظلية النهائية ♪
♪Is as quiet as tonight♪
♪ هدوء الليلة